[
  {
    "problem": "Given $2x - 5y = -17$ and $2x + 5y = 33$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 4$, $y = 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $1868$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$2384.09$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 57 & 58 \\\\ 6 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-177$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6210$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1863.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $7x^2 + 7x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.173, -0.827)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{21}}{2*7}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{21}}{2*7})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5841$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5958.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $13x^2+144x+16=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.11, -10.96}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{8} + 2x^{1} + 9x^{1}$",
    "solution": "$11x^{1} + 3x^{8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+3x-4$",
    "solution": "$(x-1)(x+4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $7030$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1757.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9 * \\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 9 \\\\ 2 & 0 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 90 & 81 \\\\ 18 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -88 & -8 & 51 & -63 & -84 & -85 & 66 & 60 & 65 & -12 \\\\ -5 & 97 & 34 & -69 & -45 & -26 & -96 & -84 & 93 & 46 \\\\ 97 & -19 & -73 & -78 & 53 & 56 & -36 & 83 & 95 & -38 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -23 & -12 & -2 & 35 & -65 & 25 & 70 \\\\ -100 & 4 & -64 & 77 & 62 & 85 & 92 \\\\ -61 & -76 & -57 & 82 & -43 & -47 & -14 \\\\ -43 & -59 & 51 & 15 & -55 & -56 & 42 \\\\ -81 & -53 & -54 & -66 & -53 & -7 & 83 \\\\ 79 & 17 & 64 & -13 & -65 & -58 & 63 \\\\ 75 & -61 & -85 & 21 & -44 & 28 & 22 \\\\ -64 & -94 & 36 & -63 & 44 & 31 & -99 \\\\ -26 & 72 & -50 & -62 & -77 & -25 & -22 \\\\ -53 & 72 & -5 & -59 & 87 & 11 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2567 & -1978 & -12976 & 474 & 10160 & 5720 & -28645 \\\\ -13781 & 27638 & -10633 & 7151 & 10116 & 5098 & 4537 \\\\ -861 & 5551 & 3415 & -19083 & -11888 & 3762 & -840 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1278$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1278.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 68 & -45 & -69 & 40 & 62 & -96 & -38 & -19 & 90 \\\\ -74 & 100 & 39 & -2 & -88 & -71 & -13 & 98 & 47 \\\\ 37 & 61 & 49 & -65 & 85 & -75 & -6 & 9 & 37 \\\\ 36 & -80 & -72 & 72 & -10 & 25 & 6 & -85 & -52 \\\\ 1 & -2 & -25 & -10 & -24 & 8 & 11 & 79 & -5 \\\\ -18 & 38 & 29 & 57 & -48 & 70 & 87 & -78 & 32 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -84 & 7 & -66 & 90 & -72 & 16 & -18 & 94 & -33 & 57 \\\\ -63 & 58 & 32 & -48 & 79 & 62 & 80 & 30 & -34 & 61 \\\\ -82 & -66 & 8 & -67 & -51 & 13 & 21 & -12 & -47 & -45 \\\\ -14 & 47 & 43 & 45 & -92 & 12 & 88 & -62 & -48 & 36 \\\\ 10 & 55 & 57 & 64 & -95 & -51 & 78 & -63 & 75 & 11 \\\\ 89 & 70 & -27 & 35 & 31 & 56 & 12 & -23 & -12 & -59 \\\\ 37 & -53 & -46 & 44 & -11 & -79 & -10 & 91 & -79 & 98 \\\\ -74 & -12 & -92 & -48 & -13 & -10 & -18 & 42 & -36 & 15 \\\\ -29 & -51 & -46 & -62 & -4 & -98 & 79 & 16 & -30 & -57 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -8313 & -1358 & 722 & 8971 & -17173 & -16285 & 8763 & -1124 & 7397 & 2883 \\\\ -19549 & -10080 & -5369 & -30470 & 16263 & 1452 & 4338 & 6562 & -12354 & 793 \\\\ -17845 & -4744 & 1723 & -5981 & -4963 & -7546 & 8074 & 5544 & 3837 & 4083 \\\\ 17057 & 8302 & 6275 & 22947 & -8892 & 2926 & -5342 & -6417 & 4556 & 3696 \\\\ -2590 & -965 & -9888 & -2843 & 3365 & -50 & -5286 & 6521 & -3769 & 2512 \\\\ 9755 & -204 & 2163 & 2144 & 4234 & 268 & 9147 & 2133 & -14262 & 2913 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2 * \\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 8 \\\\ 3 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 20 & 16 \\\\ 6 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $58x^2+107x+12=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.12, -1.72}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $2x + 5y = -44$ and $16x + -19y = 2$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -7$, $y = -6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+2x+1$",
    "solution": "$(x+1)(x+1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 * \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 9 \\\\ 7 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 88 & 99 \\\\ 77 & 99 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-13,12)$ and $(-9,-3) = $",
    "solution": "$(-11.0,4.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(7,-4)$ and $(-4,-15) = $",
    "solution": "$(1.5,-9.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(17-8j) * (-5-4j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-117-28j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $7510$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1802.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 93 & 68 \\\\ 43 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2180$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(10x-2)(-8x-10)$",
    "solution": "$-80x^2-84x+20$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -33 & -6 & -3 & -11 & -41 & 97 \\\\ 27 & -56 & 26 & -7 & 18 & -46 \\\\ -89 & 27 & -65 & -44 & -25 & -36 \\\\ -77 & -75 & 90 & 52 & -29 & -34 \\\\ -13 & 49 & 35 & 95 & -73 & 23 \\\\ -75 & -45 & -39 & 72 & -37 & -89 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -79 & 34 & 100 & -91 & 45 \\\\ 35 & -72 & -4 & 92 & 31 \\\\ -17 & 71 & -86 & -35 & -68 \\\\ -20 & -81 & 57 & 39 & 44 \\\\ -58 & 85 & 82 & 18 & 55 \\\\ -34 & -18 & -10 & -45 & 41 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 1748 & -5243 & -7977 & -2976 & -229 \\\\ -3875 & 9721 & 2225 & -6398 & -3493 \\\\ 12635 & -7498 & -7616 & 12312 & -3535 \\\\ 3726 & 3107 & -14214 & -7 & -12611 \\\\ 3699 & -15799 & -5307 & 5822 & -338 \\\\ 8745 & -9454 & -2006 & 10197 & -4634 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4+7j) * (-20-14j) = $",
    "solution": "$(18-196j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $48x^2+180x+95=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.64, -3.11}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 20 & 1 \\\\ 6 & 24 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & 1 & -4 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 6 & -5 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -4 & -45 & -9 & 15 & 2 & -52 & -100 & 44 \\\\ -61 & -29 & -36 & -79 & -25 & 28 & 38 & -46 \\\\ 85 & 84 & -95 & -31 & 28 & 26 & -34 & 66 \\\\ -87 & 0 & -25 & -32 & -80 & 70 & -11 & -11 \\\\ 72 & -21 & 40 & 40 & -98 & -51 & -70 & 63 \\\\ 38 & -15 & -39 & -8 & 69 & 63 & -3 & -6 \\\\ -71 & -50 & -39 & 87 & -53 & 90 & 76 & -26 \\\\ -25 & 28 & 81 & 7 & 3 & 100 & 25 & 86 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 14 & 11 & 60 & 63 & -35 & -2 & 22 & 79 & 0 \\\\ -39 & -70 & -99 & -92 & 87 & -34 & 62 & -51 & 73 \\\\ 48 & 12 & 20 & 80 & 10 & 16 & 3 & -98 & 84 \\\\ 94 & 1 & -95 & 79 & -20 & -42 & 7 & 74 & -17 \\\\ 45 & 41 & -79 & 79 & 91 & -13 & 6 & -89 & -30 \\\\ -38 & 35 & 97 & -86 & 6 & -24 & 32 & -5 & -35 \\\\ 59 & 53 & 64 & 91 & 61 & -86 & -13 & -28 & 41 \\\\ 25 & -80 & -6 & 25 & 59 & -67 & -5 & -35 & -64 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -57 & -7545 & -9256 & 983 & -7799 & 7638 & -3372 & 5313 & -9452 \\\\ -9974 & 6497 & 13395 & -12371 & -1671 & 3317 & -3319 & -3027 & 474 \\\\ -9644 & -11140 & -4433 & -13890 & 8527 & -5730 & 7688 & 5467 & -8689 \\\\ -12610 & -1822 & 9792 & -23625 & -4745 & 2161 & -255 & 672 & -1353 \\\\ 2480 & -11771 & 1336 & 4677 & -14524 & 3827 & -943 & 14531 & -1030 \\\\ -1123 & 6347 & 4249 & -368 & 3255 & -1603 & 2232 & 835 & -8249 \\\\ 5291 & 9423 & 9582 & -1781 & -5176 & -8701 & -2466 & 10250 & -5185 \\\\ 3064 & -3188 & 7230 & -1056 & 11453 & -10251 & 3941 & -15300 & 660 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+17x+72$",
    "solution": "$(x+9)(x+8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 1 & 3 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 3 \\\\ 0 & 1 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -1 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 4 & -3 \\\\ 0 & -1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-19, -2, 8]\\cdot[12, -20, -10]=$",
    "solution": "$-268$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x-10)(-6x-6)$",
    "solution": "$60x^2+120x+60$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-8x$",
    "solution": "$(x)(x-8)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -3x - 2$ and $y = 10/6x - 2$",
    "solution": "$(0, -2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[6, -18, 12]\\cdot[5, -9, 19]=$",
    "solution": "$420$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-19,-10)$ and $(18,-3) = $",
    "solution": "$(-0.5,-6.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $7x - 7y = 35$ and $-2x - y = 8$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -1$, $y = -6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-2x-3)(-6x+6)$",
    "solution": "$12x^2+6x-18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $45x^2+146x+32=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.24, -3.01}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $38x^2+155x+56=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.4, -3.68}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-12, -15, 9] \\times [-6, 13, -4] = $",
    "solution": "$[-57, -102, -246]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4x-6)(7x+7)$",
    "solution": "$28x^2-14x-42$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $53x^2+150x+94=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.94, -1.89}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(18,4)$ and $(0,-5) = $",
    "solution": "$(9.0,-0.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-6x+3)(-9x-5)$",
    "solution": "$54x^2+3x-15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -1/2x + 9$ and $y = -7/4x - 8$",
    "solution": "$(-68/5, 79/5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x + 8y = -90$ and $2x - 2y = -20$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = 0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $11x^2+109x+49=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.47, -9.44}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-17-5j) * (-6-19j) = $",
    "solution": "$(7+353j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{10} + 6x^{8} + 8x^{17} + 7x^{1} + 3x^{15} + 4x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{1} + 6x^{8} + 13x^{10} + 3x^{15} + 8x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-1x-56$",
    "solution": "$(x-8)(x+7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 10 \\\\ 46 & 30 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-220$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, 14, -16] \\times [12, -2, -9] = $",
    "solution": "$[-158, -354, -132]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x-2)(-7x-6)$",
    "solution": "$70x^2+74x+12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 41 & 7 & -6 & -29 & 30 & 54 & 11 \\\\ -42 & 46 & 82 & -65 & 5 & 89 & -69 \\\\ -70 & 28 & -59 & 82 & -79 & -11 & 72 \\\\ 55 & 38 & -10 & -7 & 50 & -92 & 82 \\\\ 59 & -5 & 31 & -16 & -96 & -76 & -27 \\\\ -30 & -73 & 48 & -31 & 3 & 0 & -14 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -81 & -66 & 90 & 49 & 7 & 2 & -51 & -18 & 2 & -4 \\\\ -46 & 52 & 97 & 5 & 58 & -13 & 94 & -46 & 21 & -26 \\\\ 26 & 60 & -95 & -50 & 33 & -20 & -85 & -72 & -38 & 47 \\\\ 94 & 21 & 5 & -40 & 45 & -78 & -88 & 37 & 49 & 44 \\\\ -54 & -88 & -97 & -28 & 12 & 34 & -80 & 50 & 7 & 16 \\\\ 69 & -31 & -46 & 31 & 15 & -6 & 70 & 31 & 38 & -16 \\\\ 36 & 67 & 36 & -50 & 54 & -6 & -11 & -70 & -74 & 75 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -4023 & -6888 & -204 & 3788 & 954 & 3003 & 2888 & 703 & 484 & -1463 \\\\ 695 & 897 & -14496 & 2741 & -176 & 2798 & 11805 & -1830 & 3104 & -6553 \\\\ 16655 & 16375 & 13192 & -5349 & 5652 & -8772 & 8759 & -2077 & 409 & 4699 \\\\ -13217 & 1545 & 11885 & -4687 & 5592 & 2122 & -9109 & -8369 & -8269 & 6436 \\\\ -6279 & 6365 & 13636 & 3638 & -3324 & -1835 & -2049 & -8922 & -3511 & -1698 \\\\ 3456 & -789 & -15291 & -2379 & -4975 & 2533 & -6770 & 425 & -3879 & 1908 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 8x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.394, -7.606)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{52}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{52}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7/6x - 6$ and $y = 7/4x + 6$",
    "solution": "$(-144/35, -6/5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-2x - 3y = 45$ and $4x - 7y = 27$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -9$, $y = -9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-12x + -6y = 276$ and $7x + 9y = -260$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -14$, $y = -18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(4-15j) * (8+4j) = $",
    "solution": "$(92-104j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(3x+5)(6x-8)$",
    "solution": "$18x^2+6x-40$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -87 & -56 & -53 & -33 & 32 \\\\ 74 & -17 & -30 & 97 & -18 \\\\ -34 & -25 & -19 & -58 & -37 \\\\ 23 & -72 & -6 & 33 & 76 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 61 & -78 & -24 \\\\ 69 & 11 & 35 \\\\ 19 & 91 & 51 \\\\ -97 & -24 & -100 \\\\ 24 & 43 & -96 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -6209 & 3515 & -2347 \\\\ -7070 & -11791 & -11873 \\\\ 578 & 449 & 8324 \\\\ -5056 & -656 & -13974 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{3} + 4x^{3} + 10x^{15} + 4x^{5} + 7x^{14} + 3x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{3} + 4x^{5} + 3x^{9} + 7x^{14} + 10x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12 * \\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 4 \\\\ 7 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 60 & 48 \\\\ 84 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(18, -16)$ and $(21, -20)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -x - 9$ and $y = -3/4x - 2$",
    "solution": "$(-28, 19)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-8, -1)$ and $(-14, -14)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{205}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 68 & -44 & -45 & -97 & 81 & 76 \\\\ -4 & 4 & 75 & -42 & -4 & -67 \\\\ 66 & -93 & -25 & -45 & 10 & -90 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 87 & 42 & -56 & 58 \\\\ -6 & 39 & -37 & -100 \\\\ -85 & -43 & 74 & 1 \\\\ -57 & -80 & -41 & 93 \\\\ -9 & 56 & -2 & 3 \\\\ 100 & 15 & 61 & 71 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 22405 & 16511 & 2941 & 4917 \\\\ -11017 & -1106 & 3269 & -9232 \\\\ 1900 & 3030 & -5770 & 2558 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-18+17j) * (-12+13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-5-438j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$12 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 4 \\\\ 8 & 6 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 84 & 48 \\\\ 96 & 72 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(729)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9+6j) * 6j = $",
    "solution": "$(-36+54j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 0 \\\\ 8 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 21 & 0 \\\\ 24 & 15 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[7, -6, -17]\\cdot[-18, 19, 5]=$",
    "solution": "$-325$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 9/3x - 10$ and $y = 1/4x - 10$",
    "solution": "$(0, -10)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[12, 0, -3]\\cdot[10, -3, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 1 & 2 \\\\ 2 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & -2 \\\\ 0 & -1 & 2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1905$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$381.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 9 & 1 & 4 \\\\ 10 & 1 & 5 \\\\ 8 & 1 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & -1 \\\\ 0 & -4 & 5 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-7+7j) * (-9-2j) = $",
    "solution": "$(77-49j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-6, 5)$ and $(-20, -15)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{596}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-2, 12, -10] \\times [-18, 1, -14] = $",
    "solution": "$[-158, 152, 214]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-4, 10, -10] \\times [-14, -3, -10] = $",
    "solution": "$[-130, 100, 152]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-19, 0, 12]\\cdot[-18, -16, -1]=$",
    "solution": "$330$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(10+16j) * (5-17j) = $",
    "solution": "$(322-90j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 4 & 1 \\\\ 15 & 16 & 5 \\\\ 3 & 3 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -1 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -5 \\\\ -3 & 0 & 4 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 63 & 10 \\\\ 39 & 96 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$5658$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[17, 5, 3]\\cdot[15, 7, 13]=$",
    "solution": "$329$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, -17, 10]\\cdot[-19, -14, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$161$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 94 & 82 \\\\ 29 & 43 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1664$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5918$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$12776.52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{13} + 8x^{10} + 5x^{3} + 1x^{10} + 5x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{3} + 5x^{5} + 9x^{10} + 10x^{13}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-10, 5)$ and $(-6, 2)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{25}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7 * \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 3 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 49 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 21 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 11 & 43 \\\\ 67 & 91 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-1880$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $13x^2+68x+76=0$",
    "solution": "${-3.61, -1.62}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{19} + 5x^{19} + 1x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{5} + 12x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{5} + 6x^{15} + 1x^{15}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{5} + 7x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-7x-8$",
    "solution": "$(x-8)(x+1)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{10} + 6x^{8} + 5x^{16} + 4x^{4} + 10x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{4} + 6x^{8} + 17x^{10} + 5x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $7x^2+109x+25=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.23, -15.34}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-3x - 6y = 66$ and $-3x - 5y = 59$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -8$, $y = -7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 5/3x - 7$ and $y = 3/5x + 10$",
    "solution": "$(255/16, 313/16)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{12}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2108$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$2371.21$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{11} + 10x^{9} + 8x^{12} + 9x^{10} + 3x^{8} + 6x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$3x^{8} + 10x^{9} + 15x^{10} + 7x^{11} + 8x^{12}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-1, -3, 15] \\times [16, 15, 7] = $",
    "solution": "$[-246, 247, 33]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2936$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5869.08$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-10,3)$ and $(15,-3) = $",
    "solution": "$(2.5,0.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2990$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6409.33$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$8x^{11} + 1x^{3} + 2x^{3} + 10x^{1} + 3x^{15}$",
    "solution": "$10x^{1} + 3x^{3} + 8x^{11} + 3x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $2x + 14y = 92$ and $-9x + 1y = 162$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -17$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5605$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$10037.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $58x^2+184x+18=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.1, -3.07}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-14x + -6y = -102$ and $-14x + 13y = -444$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 15$, $y = -18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+7x-18$",
    "solution": "$(x+9)(x-2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 8/4x + 10$ and $y = -9/3x - 5$",
    "solution": "$(-3, 4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10 * \\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 40 & 10 \\\\ 10 & 50 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1387$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$624.15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-2x-8$",
    "solution": "$(x+2)(x-4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[0, -16, -3] \\times [4, 4, 3] = $",
    "solution": "$[-36, -12, 64]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[3, 19, 1] \\times [-14, -12, -18] = $",
    "solution": "$[-330, 40, 230]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5990$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6616.69$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[4, -10, -9] \\times [-14, -9, -4] = $",
    "solution": "$[-41, 142, -176]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[7, -19, -3] \\times [16, -16, 0] = $",
    "solution": "$[-48, -48, 192]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 8/6x$ and $y = 5x + 8$",
    "solution": "$(-24/11, -32/11)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $2x + 17y = -38$ and $9x + 6y = -30$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -2$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $5x^2 + 8x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.6, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-8 + 2}{2*5}, \\frac{-8 - 2}{2*5})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 56 & 51 \\\\ 77 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-3255$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 21 & 77 \\\\ 20 & 52 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-448$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $37x^2+186x+33=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.18, -4.84}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 35 & 3 \\\\ 19 & 65 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2218$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $59x^2+189x+93=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.61, -2.6}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $7809$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$3514.05$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -17 & 30 \\\\ 68 & -85 \\\\ 82 & 58 \\\\ -77 & -71 \\\\ 35 & -21 \\\\ 41 & 54 \\\\ -66 & -8 \\\\ 60 & 42 \\\\ 97 & 5 \\\\ 76 & 91 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 19 & 46 & -29 & 73 & -40 & -85 & -47 & 12 & -65 \\\\ 69 & -33 & -86 & 27 & -73 & 67 & 14 & -71 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 1747 & -1772 & -2087 & -431 & -1510 & 3455 & 1219 & -2334 & 1045 \\\\ -4573 & 5933 & 5338 & 2669 & 3485 & -11475 & -4386 & 6851 & -4250 \\\\ 5560 & 1858 & -7366 & 7552 & -7514 & -3084 & -3042 & -3134 & -5446 \\\\ -6362 & -1199 & 8339 & -7538 & 8263 & 1788 & 2625 & 4117 & 5147 \\\\ -784 & 2303 & 791 & 1988 & 133 & -4382 & -1939 & 1911 & -2233 \\\\ 4505 & 104 & -5833 & 4451 & -5582 & 133 & -1171 & -3342 & -2773 \\\\ -1806 & -2772 & 2602 & -5034 & 3224 & 5074 & 2990 & -224 & 4306 \\\\ 4038 & 1374 & -5352 & 5514 & -5466 & -2286 & -2232 & -2262 & -3984 \\\\ 2188 & 4297 & -3243 & 7216 & -4245 & -7910 & -4489 & 809 & -6315 \\\\ 7723 & 493 & -10030 & 8005 & -9683 & -363 & -2298 & -5549 & -5122 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5380$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1883.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $7x + -5y = -90$ and $-14x + -6y = 228$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -15$, $y = -3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-3, 1)$ and $(12, -3)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{241}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-4, -12)$ and $(-18, -8)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{212}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 10 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & -4 & 5 \\\\ -2 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{5} + 3x^{10} + 4x^{17} + 3x^{15} + 8x^{5} + 8x^{17} + 10x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$11x^{5} + 3x^{10} + 3x^{15} + 22x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{18} + 6x^{10} + 8x^{13}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{10} + 8x^{13} + 9x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-8x - 2y = -76$ and $4x - 5y = 2$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 8$, $y = 6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $7x + 2y = 23$ and $7x - 3y = -17$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 1$, $y = 8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{1} + 10x^{18} + 7x^{9} + 3x^{13} + 5x^{9} + 9x^{5}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{1} + 9x^{5} + 12x^{9} + 3x^{13} + 10x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{14} + 8x^{13} + 6x^{15} + 1x^{10} + 6x^{15} + 6x^{13}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{10} + 14x^{13} + 9x^{14} + 12x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(0,-4)$ and $(-2,-19) = $",
    "solution": "$(-1.0,-11.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-14x + -16y = -308$ and $19x + 15y = 324$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = 14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 1 & 0 \\\\ 1 & 8 & 4 \\\\ 1 & 10 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 5 & -4 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\\\ -2 & -1 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-3x + 13y = 69$ and $-9x + 5y = -99$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 16$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $94x^2+148x+52=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.53, -1.05}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-3x + 5y = 47$ and $8x + 10y = -32$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -9$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 2 & 1 & 8 \\\\ 3 & 1 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -4 & -1 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 3 & -2 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$-20j * (-6-16j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-320+120j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-5,-12)$ and $(-19,-9) = $",
    "solution": "$(-12.0,-10.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, -20, -8] \\times [-6, 5, -12] = $",
    "solution": "$[280, 180, -65]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -x - 8$ and $y = -2/4x - 10$",
    "solution": "$(4, -12)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 9x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.347, -8.653)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{69}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{69}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(12+10j) * -9j = $",
    "solution": "$(90-108j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 28 & 15 \\\\ 39 & 49 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$787$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $6x + 7y = 78$ and $-8x + 2y = -36$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = 6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[10, -10, 2] \\times [-12, -20, 4] = $",
    "solution": "$[0, -64, -320]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$13 * \\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 0 \\\\ 6 & 6 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 52 & 0 \\\\ 78 & 78 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -80 & -32 & 80 \\\\ 60 & -62 & 48 \\\\ 100 & -82 & -22 \\\\ 61 & 94 & -18 \\\\ 58 & -26 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 45 & 87 & 2 & 39 \\\\ 30 & 38 & -22 & 76 \\\\ 38 & 78 & 20 & -94 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -1520 & -1936 & 2144 & -13072 \\\\ 2664 & 6608 & 2444 & -6884 \\\\ 1204 & 3868 & 1564 & -264 \\\\ 4881 & 7475 & -2306 & 11215 \\\\ 1830 & 4058 & 688 & 286 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6822$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$5457.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(2)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $2622$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3001.93$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $8031$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1606.2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $2x^2 + 5x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.5, -2.0)) = (\\frac{-5 + 3}{2*2}, \\frac{-5 - 3}{2*2})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $8157$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$5138.91$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-14x + -7y = -175$ and $20x + 13y = 289$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = 13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $8774$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$13167.41$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 64 & 49 \\\\ 32 & 71 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2976$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 49 & 77 \\\\ 93 & 59 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-4270$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{18} + 2x^{3} + 9x^{13} + 7x^{18} + 7x^{2}$",
    "solution": "$7x^{2} + 2x^{3} + 9x^{13} + 17x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 73 & 58 \\\\ 48 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2711$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $8x + 6y = -2$ and $3x - 2y = 29$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 5$, $y = -7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4 * \\begin{bmatrix} 9 & 2 \\\\ 1 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 36 & 8 \\\\ 4 & 36 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5234$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $1$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5495.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9x+4)(-9x-3)$",
    "solution": "$-81x^2-63x-12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[20, -20, -2]\\cdot[-13, 15, -1]=$",
    "solution": "$-558$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x-8)(-7x+7)$",
    "solution": "$x^2+56x-56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $ - 3y = -9$ and $-5x - 4y = 13$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -5$, $y = 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -73 & -73 & -55 & -22 & 73 & -98 \\\\ -74 & 75 & -57 & 12 & -75 & -17 \\\\ -5 & -32 & -41 & 13 & 71 & 68 \\\\ -38 & -2 & -16 & -12 & -78 & -99 \\\\ -36 & -14 & 34 & 17 & 36 & 82 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -14 & -72 \\\\ 61 & 75 \\\\ 44 & -55 \\\\ 36 & 16 \\\\ -65 & 99 \\\\ -67 & 68 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -4822 & 3017 \\\\ 9549 & 5699 \\\\ -12389 & 12076 \\\\ 10977 & -11180 \\\\ -6076 & 9084 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 5x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.697, -4.303)) = (\\frac{-5 + \\sqrt{13}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-5 - \\sqrt{13}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-2x - 7y = 66$ and $6x - 5y = 62$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 2$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $4367$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$131.01$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 7x + 9 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.697, -5.303)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{13}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{13}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-7x + 9y = 21$ and $-12x + 12y = 12$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(20,0)$ and $(9,4) = $",
    "solution": "$(14.5,2.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-8x + 17y = -19$ and $3x + -6y = 9$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 13$, $y = 5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 1 & 15 \\\\ 8 & 2 & 25 \\\\ 4 & 1 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & -3 & 5 \\\\ -4 & 0 & 5 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -2 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-3-15j) * (-20-6j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-30+318j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(2, 18)$ and $(-14, 1)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{545}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 19 & 22 \\\\ 70 & 15 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-1255$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x+7)(5x+1)$",
    "solution": "$5x^2+36x+7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & -81 \\\\ 69 & 45 \\\\ 33 & 74 \\\\ 59 & -58 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 32 & -82 & 14 & -67 & 95 & -36 & 48 & 10 \\\\ -83 & 21 & -23 & 24 & -9 & 64 & -58 & -65 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 6691 & -1619 & 1849 & -1877 & 634 & -5148 & 4650 & 5255 \\\\ -1527 & -4713 & -69 & -3543 & 6150 & 396 & 702 & -2235 \\\\ -5086 & -1152 & -1240 & -435 & 2469 & 3548 & -2708 & -4480 \\\\ 6702 & -6056 & 2160 & -5345 & 6127 & -5836 & 6196 & 4360 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -63 & 45 & -79 & -14 & 62 & -64 \\\\ 75 & 10 & 91 & 4 & 78 & -40 \\\\ 66 & 98 & -73 & -97 & -98 & 40 \\\\ 46 & 28 & -49 & -46 & -9 & 29 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 33 & -47 & 92 & -38 & 46 & 57 & 18 & 16 & 63 & -12 \\\\ -12 & 22 & -39 & 31 & 39 & -88 & 61 & -21 & -98 & -77 \\\\ -42 & 53 & 2 & -89 & -47 & 32 & -13 & -54 & -83 & -58 \\\\ -68 & 2 & -76 & -66 & 100 & -64 & -46 & -75 & -29 & 15 \\\\ -4 & -98 & -3 & -89 & 90 & 87 & 22 & -73 & -46 & 69 \\\\ 59 & -44 & -84 & -83 & 41 & -58 & 95 & -36 & -5 & 97 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -2373 & -3524 & -1455 & 11538 & 4126 & -77 & -1434 & 1141 & -3948 & -267 \\\\ -4411 & -4358 & 9514 & -14525 & 5343 & 15157 & -1491 & -8478 & -7312 & -5386 \\\\ 13416 & 2835 & 6410 & 18831 & -6591 & -11836 & 14221 & 15929 & 7734 & -8441 \\\\ 8115 & -4629 & 4129 & 4911 & 1290 & -931 & 7846 & 5857 & 5824 & 1636 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-1x + 11y = 0$ and $-7x + 3y = -74$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 11$, $y = 1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$1x^{14} + 8x^{5} + 8x^{9} + 5x^{3} + 10x^{15} + 7x^{6} + 8x^{11}$",
    "solution": "$5x^{3} + 8x^{5} + 7x^{6} + 8x^{9} + 8x^{11} + 1x^{14} + 10x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[20, 17, -6] \\times [-4, -15, -12] = $",
    "solution": "$[-294, 264, -232]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $13x + -5y = 101$ and $1x + -4y = 15$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 7$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-5, 12, -3]\\cdot[16, 6, -1]=$",
    "solution": "$-5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 6x + 8 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-2.0, -4.0)) = (\\frac{-6 + 2}{2*1}, \\frac{-6 - 2}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 63 & -27 & 89 & 12 & 83 & 94 & -19 & -46 \\\\ 91 & 18 & 67 & -57 & 75 & 20 & -60 & 7 & 77 \\\\ -55 & -7 & -27 & 92 & 26 & 33 & 38 & -46 & 23 \\\\ 36 & -37 & 20 & -100 & -46 & 78 & 85 & 63 & 39 \\\\ 64 & -86 & 19 & -94 & 76 & -27 & 17 & 80 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 67 & 68 & 83 \\\\ 41 & 47 & 24 \\\\ -21 & -98 & 33 \\\\ -50 & -55 & -1 \\\\ -39 & 8 & -38 \\\\ -11 & 75 & 3 \\\\ 34 & -54 & 59 \\\\ -18 & 75 & 82 \\\\ -33 & 73 & 49 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2710 & -2486 & 2474 \\\\ 426 & 15089 & 8270 \\\\ -8021 & -7623 & -7008 \\\\ 6880 & 12713 & 16934 \\\\ 1138 & 8159 & 9151 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8x-2)(8x-8)$",
    "solution": "$64x^2-80x+16$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-12, 6, -3] \\times [6, 8, 18] = $",
    "solution": "$[132, 198, -132]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -77 & -45 & -45 & -19 & -83 & -36 \\\\ -83 & 27 & -68 & -64 & -90 & 53 \\\\ 17 & 46 & 20 & 38 & 25 & 11 \\\\ 25 & -89 & -24 & -47 & -53 & 11 \\\\ 93 & -42 & -96 & -56 & -99 & -56 \\\\ 33 & 49 & -11 & 59 & -85 & -82 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 21 & -3 & 74 & -39 & -70 & 18 & 36 & -41 & 100 & 87 \\\\ -78 & 49 & -9 & -65 & -35 & 88 & 9 & 30 & -57 & 74 \\\\ -35 & 13 & 21 & -74 & -69 & 41 & 100 & 12 & -35 & -3 \\\\ -9 & -15 & -84 & -91 & 43 & 76 & -79 & -38 & -9 & -25 \\\\ 1 & -29 & 69 & 81 & 2 & 90 & 25 & -73 & 85 & -31 \\\\ -33 & -18 & 4 & -2 & -59 & 42 & -53 & -66 & 95 & 38 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4744 & 781 & -10513 & 4336 & 11211 & -17617 & -6343 & 10424 & -13864 & -8214 \\\\ -2732 & 3304 & -8435 & 4942 & 3498 & -12644 & -9548 & 8901 & -9498 & 1385 \\\\ -4611 & 970 & -159 & -6588 & -3145 & 10774 & 66 & -3072 & 1206 & 3516 \\\\ 8314 & -2704 & 2482 & 6548 & 245 & -16246 & -496 & 946 & 5376 & -1103 \\\\ 10842 & 1134 & 2893 & 3396 & 2282 & -21476 & -1713 & 6826 & 1823 & 7612 \\\\ -654 & 5215 & -9379 & -15748 & 3939 & -2155 & -1911 & 9360 & -14654 & 4574 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-14,-3)$ and $(6,-12) = $",
    "solution": "$(-4.0,-7.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 51 & 53 \\\\ 11 & 42 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1559$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 96 & 53 \\\\ 17 & 100 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$8699$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 3 \\\\ 1 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & -3 \\\\ -1 & 1 & 2 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-13+0j) * (10+18j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-130-234j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4x - 10$ and $y = -6/5x - 2$",
    "solution": "$(20/13, -50/13)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-11, 18, -18] \\times [5, 17, -3] = $",
    "solution": "$[252, -123, -277]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 2/6x + 8$ and $y = -8/4x - 7$",
    "solution": "$(-45/7, 41/7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{3} + 7x^{8} + 6x^{17} + 9x^{9} + 2x^{17} + 4x^{5} + 8x^{5} + 2x^{10} + 9x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$10x^{3} + 12x^{5} + 7x^{8} + 9x^{9} + 2x^{10} + 9x^{12} + 8x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 9x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.228, -8.772)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{73}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{73}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $8x^2 + 8x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.146, -0.854)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*8}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*8})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{8} + 9x^{15} + 10x^{9} + 1x^{6} + 5x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{6} + 9x^{8} + 10x^{9} + 5x^{12} + 9x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 43 \\\\ 71 & 35 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2773$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{13} + 7x^{6} + 9x^{5} + 3x^{3} + 3x^{3}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{3} + 9x^{5} + 7x^{6} + 7x^{13}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 8x + 8 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.172, -6.828)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{6} + 4x^{14} + 10x^{13} + 3x^{12} + 5x^{17} + 3x^{16} + 10x^{11} + 8x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{6} + 8x^{9} + 10x^{11} + 3x^{12} + 10x^{13} + 4x^{14} + 3x^{16} + 5x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3723$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1116.9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $8x + -3y = 22$ and $-7x + 1y = -16$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 2$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-15x+54$",
    "solution": "$(x-9)(x-6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9977$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$14740.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3048$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $1$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$182.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 7x + 4 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.628, -6.372)) = (\\frac{-7 + \\sqrt{33}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-7 - \\sqrt{33}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 76 & -95 & -67 & 6 & -100 & 89 & 75 & -80 & 31 & -51 \\\\ -66 & -62 & 20 & -81 & -59 & -89 & -9 & -28 & 34 & -93 \\\\ 51 & 70 & -99 & -46 & -35 & 0 & -65 & -99 & -77 & 99 \\\\ 49 & 92 & -42 & -74 & -40 & 35 & 92 & 59 & 14 & -94 \\\\ 49 & 97 & 69 & -63 & 99 & 97 & -87 & 48 & -83 & -94 \\\\ 5 & -68 & -62 & 78 & -73 & 9 & -53 & 74 & 30 & -94 \\\\ 57 & -40 & -32 & 15 & 75 & -35 & -67 & 11 & -17 & 37 \\\\ -25 & 76 & -76 & 3 & 39 & -8 & 69 & 99 & -25 & -42 \\\\ -1 & 50 & -4 & -2 & 68 & 18 & 79 & -21 & -80 & 49 \\\\ 21 & 61 & -74 & -22 & 14 & 19 & 79 & 47 & 18 & -40 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -4 & -96 \\\\ 54 & 10 \\\\ -35 & -8 \\\\ 56 & 5 \\\\ 85 & 14 \\\\ 7 & -73 \\\\ -25 & -16 \\\\ 60 & -52 \\\\ -14 & -77 \\\\ -19 & -50 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -16770 & -12454 \\\\ -14122 & 14454 \\\\ -3628 & 3043 \\\\ 1773 & -7851 \\\\ 16196 & -309 \\\\ 3835 & -2563 \\\\ 7572 & -1977 \\\\ 15654 & 2686 \\\\ 5592 & 3794 \\\\ 7244 & -5209 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-7, -4, -4]\\cdot[0, -12, -19]=$",
    "solution": "$124$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 22 & 38 \\\\ 31 & -54 \\\\ 58 & -91 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 5 & -29 & -84 & -89 & 19 & 45 & -86 \\\\ 63 & -52 & -10 & 97 & 80 & -18 & -53 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2504 & -2614 & -2228 & 1728 & 3458 & 306 & -3906 \\\\ -3247 & 1909 & -2064 & -7997 & -3731 & 2367 & 196 \\\\ -5443 & 3050 & -3962 & -13989 & -6178 & 4248 & -165 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7316$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$10261.07$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $47x^2+114x+60=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.77, -1.65}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $2580$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1032.0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-18-4j) * (19-8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-374+68j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $3x + 4y = -71$ and $15x + 16y = -311$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -9$, $y = -11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4/5x - 9$ and $y = x + 2$",
    "solution": "$(-55, -53)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $3930$ dollars, $6$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$4415.75$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9035$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$21389.13$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9x+8)(3x-9)$",
    "solution": "$27x^2-57x-72$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $5x^2 + 8x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.6, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-8 + 2}{2*5}, \\frac{-8 - 2}{2*5})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-1, 8)$ and $(-7, -10)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{360}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 76 & 32 \\\\ 51 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-1404$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -2/6x - 9$ and $y = 4$",
    "solution": "$(-39, 4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-20, 10, -18]\\cdot[16, 0, -9]=$",
    "solution": "$-158$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-3x + 11y = 137$ and $-14x + 12y = 364$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -20$, $y = 7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6 * \\begin{bmatrix} 5 & 3 \\\\ 5 & 10 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 30 & 18 \\\\ 30 & 60 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-16x + 19y = -167$ and $-19x + -8y = -290$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 14$, $y = 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(12, -1)$ and $(-8, -18)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{689}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-16, 20)$ and $(19, 18)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1229}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(5, -9)$ and $(-1, -11)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{40}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(19, 18)$ and $(-2, -17)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1666}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 41 & -100 & 41 & 11 \\\\ -19 & -56 & 28 & -11 \\\\ 39 & -56 & -3 & 82 \\\\ 50 & 18 & -45 & -95 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 76 & -4 & 43 & -25 & -65 & -37 & -18 & 29 & -90 & 93 \\\\ 85 & -55 & 72 & -58 & -47 & 91 & 45 & 25 & 19 & 77 \\\\ 32 & -60 & 64 & 42 & -24 & 87 & -71 & 35 & 62 & -39 \\\\ -25 & 77 & 71 & 34 & -10 & -92 & 40 & -51 & 1 & 99 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -4347 & 3723 & -2032 & 6871 & 941 & -8062 & -7709 & -437 & -3037 & -4397 \\\\ -5033 & 629 & -3838 & 4525 & 3305 & -945 & -4606 & -410 & 2371 & -8260 \\\\ -3942 & 9418 & 3275 & 4935 & -651 & -14344 & 271 & -4556 & -4678 & 7550 \\\\ 6265 & -5805 & -6179 & -7414 & -2066 & 4613 & -695 & 5170 & -7043 & -1614 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(256)=$",
    "solution": "$8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(11,-5)$ and $(-13,6) = $",
    "solution": "$(-1.0,0.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & 4 \\\\ 2 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & -4 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 7 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-3x + 3y = 57$ and $-2x - 4y = -16$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = 9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 35 & -27 & -90 \\\\ -37 & 83 & -75 \\\\ 76 & -43 & 58 \\\\ 30 & 10 & 33 \\\\ -6 & -39 & 86 \\\\ 85 & 37 & 9 \\\\ -82 & -71 & 59 \\\\ 71 & -50 & -79 \\\\ 85 & 49 & 86 \\\\ -9 & 87 & -65 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 83 & -84 & -57 & -92 & 46 & -6 & 54 & -45 \\\\ 42 & 12 & 91 & -78 & -26 & -31 & -59 & -39 \\\\ 86 & 78 & 50 & -41 & -37 & -33 & -93 & -62 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -5969 & -10284 & -8952 & 2576 & 5642 & 3597 & 11853 & 5058 \\\\ -6035 & -1746 & 5912 & 5 & -1085 & 124 & 80 & 3078 \\\\ 9490 & -2376 & -5345 & -6016 & 2468 & -1037 & 1247 & -5339 \\\\ 5748 & 174 & 850 & -4893 & -101 & -1579 & -2039 & -3786 \\\\ 5260 & 6744 & 1093 & 68 & -2444 & -1593 & -6021 & -3541 \\\\ 9383 & -5994 & -1028 & -11075 & 2615 & -1954 & 1570 & -5826 \\\\ -4714 & 10638 & 1163 & 10663 & -4109 & 746 & -5726 & 2801 \\\\ -3001 & -12726 & -12547 & 607 & 7489 & 3731 & 14131 & 3653 \\\\ 16509 & 156 & 3914 & -15168 & -546 & -4867 & -6299 & -11068 \\\\ -2683 & -3270 & 5180 & -3293 & -271 & -498 & 426 & 1042 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9637$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1349.18$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9x-9)(-4x+3)$",
    "solution": "$-36x^2+63x-27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 8x + 9 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-1.354, -6.646)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{28}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{28}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $9x^2 + 9x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.333, -0.667)) = (\\frac{-9 + 3}{2*9}, \\frac{-9 - 3}{2*9})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $8x^2 + 9x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.305, -0.82)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{17}}{2*8}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{17}}{2*8})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{16} + 9x^{6} + 10x^{15} + 9x^{13} + 5x^{15} + 10x^{7}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{6} + 10x^{7} + 9x^{13} + 15x^{15} + 9x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 6 & 1 & 6 \\\\ 5 & 1 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 0 & -5 & 6 \\\\ 1 & 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(12, -17)$ and $(-5, 10)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{1018}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(12, -14)$ and $(4, 9)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{593}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $55x^2+135x+20=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.16, -2.3}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-3x-10$",
    "solution": "$(x+2)(x-5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+4x-32$",
    "solution": "$(x+8)(x-4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $8x + 19y = -340$ and $6x + -20y = 156$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -14$, $y = -12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{12}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{12}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $6x + 13y = -215$ and $-4x + -1y = 59$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -12$, $y = -11$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-6x+3)(7x-5)$",
    "solution": "$-42x^2+51x-15$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-19-9j) * (14-20j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-446+254j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x+9)(5x+3)$",
    "solution": "$5x^2+48x+27$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-5, -15, 5]\\cdot[-7, -2, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$150$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 14 & 23 \\\\ 98 & 18 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2002$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-5, 1)$ and $(9, -16)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{485}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-14, 9, 6] \\times [-18, -5, -15] = $",
    "solution": "$[-105, -318, 232]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $72x^2+185x+72=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.48, -2.09}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -34 & 80 & -74 & 35 & 95 & 17 \\\\ -6 & 75 & 14 & 30 & -78 & -63 \\\\ 1 & -42 & -11 & 16 & -47 & -92 \\\\ 26 & 79 & -87 & 2 & 28 & -95 \\\\ -24 & -45 & 71 & -85 & 2 & -21 \\\\ 86 & -80 & 11 & 95 & -66 & 100 \\\\ 95 & 88 & -43 & 13 & 91 & 30 \\\\ -75 & -21 & 61 & -69 & 51 & 52 \\\\ 30 & -17 & -2 & -78 & -52 & 50 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 43 & 73 & 98 & -65 & 27 & 49 & -90 & -91 & -30 \\\\ -76 & -8 & 81 & 72 & 30 & -65 & 73 & -25 & -50 \\\\ 64 & 24 & 73 & 19 & 40 & -6 & -80 & -27 & -64 \\\\ 15 & -25 & -85 & 57 & -53 & -56 & 58 & -26 & 41 \\\\ -9 & 77 & 30 & 44 & -36 & -55 & -30 & 5 & 13 \\\\ -12 & -90 & -35 & -95 & -52 & -23 & 9 & 18 & 94 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -12812 & 12 & -2974 & 11124 & -7637 & -13998 & 14153 & 2963 & 6024 \\\\ -3154 & -1788 & 3824 & 10319 & 7142 & -1194 & 8408 & -4011 & -10172 \\\\ 4298 & 4406 & -3657 & 4286 & 3955 & 6650 & -766 & -1051 & -5829 \\\\ -9536 & 9834 & 6591 & 12716 & 3418 & -2806 & 8808 & -3614 & -7646 \\\\ 5891 & 4481 & 7206 & -3093 & 6367 & 6456 & -11984 & 3234 & -7007 \\\\ 11301 & -9275 & -10804 & -18130 & -7497 & 5358 & -6070 & -7123 & 13153 \\\\ -6339 & 9181 & 13874 & 1239 & -2040 & -7230 & -392 & -9027 & 38 \\\\ 157 & -2871 & 977 & -2107 & -1098 & -2813 & -4727 & 8688 & 2118 \\\\ 1152 & -4276 & 4737 & -14696 & 3626 & 8665 & -6295 & 417 & 904 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-7, 0)$ and $(16, -6)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{565}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-2x$",
    "solution": "$(x-2)(x)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $90x^2+120x+19=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.18, -1.15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7 * \\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 4 \\\\ 10 & 8 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 28 & 28 \\\\ 70 & 56 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{1} + 9x^{7} + 4x^{15} + 9x^{8} + 10x^{2} + 6x^{14} + 10x^{19} + 8x^{17} + 9x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{1} + 10x^{2} + 9x^{7} + 9x^{8} + 9x^{10} + 6x^{14} + 4x^{15} + 8x^{17} + 10x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5+11j) * (14+20j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-290+54j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[12, -1, 6]\\cdot[18, 10, -19]=$",
    "solution": "$92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $7049$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8259.03$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $55x^2+182x+69=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.44, -2.87}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $26x^2+161x+99=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.69, -5.5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 40 & 51 \\\\ 28 & 75 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1572$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+10x+24$",
    "solution": "$(x+4)(x+6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-17, -10)$ and $(-8, -18)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{145}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(2187)=$",
    "solution": "$7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $40x^2+191x+87=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.51, -4.27}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10x^{15} + 10x^{9} + 4x^{7} + 8x^{10} + 5x^{18} + 2x^{15}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{7} + 10x^{9} + 8x^{10} + 12x^{15} + 5x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 * \\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 0 \\\\ 9 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 66 & 0 \\\\ 99 & 11 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $2x + 4y = 0$ and $8x + 9y = -21$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -6$, $y = 3$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7/3x - 9$ and $y = -1/2x + 6$",
    "solution": "$(-90/11, 111/11)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-9x$",
    "solution": "$(x)(x-9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + 18y = -265$ and $-14x + 16y = 166$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -13$, $y = -1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6716$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $3$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$2014.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 76 & 40 \\\\ 41 & 97 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$5732$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-17-2j) * (-2-19j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-4+327j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1191$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$190.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-2,12)$ and $(-4,3) = $",
    "solution": "$(-3.0,7.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $6x - 3y = 30$ and $-7x - 8y = 80$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 0$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 48 & 25 & -11 & -40 & -55 & -99 & -9 & 12 \\\\ 13 & -30 & -15 & -75 & 53 & 85 & 67 & -96 \\\\ 67 & 66 & -95 & 8 & 0 & -42 & 79 & 45 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 70 & 58 & -37 & 82 & 13 \\\\ -79 & -12 & -100 & -79 & -75 \\\\ -60 & 15 & 37 & -47 & 55 \\\\ 73 & -90 & -42 & -41 & 66 \\\\ 16 & -53 & -66 & 0 & 32 \\\\ -37 & 49 & 82 & 71 & -13 \\\\ 61 & -76 & -71 & 92 & -76 \\\\ 57 & 91 & -6 & -17 & -53 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 2043 & 5759 & -6924 & -3943 & -4921 \\\\ -4977 & -4833 & 4405 & 21047 & -2769 \\\\ 14698 & -3018 & -22253 & 7938 & -16619 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9991$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$14627.82$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 5 & 5 \\\\ 2 & 10 & 11 \\\\ 1 & 6 & 6 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 6 & 0 & -5 \\\\ 1 & -1 & 1 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-11,13)$ and $(-9,-1) = $",
    "solution": "$(-10.0,6.0)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$9x^{8} + 1x^{18} + 2x^{19} + 9x^{4}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{4} + 9x^{8} + 1x^{18} + 2x^{19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 47 & -97 & -83 \\\\ -95 & 0 & -63 \\\\ 45 & -31 & 31 \\\\ 67 & -39 & 81 \\\\ 90 & 49 & -63 \\\\ -17 & -32 & -62 \\\\ 34 & 11 & -7 \\\\ 16 & 61 & -23 \\\\ 75 & -38 & -40 \\\\ -28 & -88 & 15 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -76 & 56 & -55 \\\\ 66 & 57 & -14 \\\\ 96 & -19 & -17 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -17942 & -1320 & 184 \\\\ 1172 & -4123 & 6296 \\\\ -2490 & 164 & -2568 \\\\ 110 & -10 & -4516 \\\\ -9654 & 9030 & -4565 \\\\ -6772 & -1598 & 2437 \\\\ -2530 & 2664 & -1905 \\\\ 602 & 4810 & -1343 \\\\ -12048 & 2794 & -2913 \\\\ -2240 & -6869 & 2517 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(5,13)$ and $(-16,8) = $",
    "solution": "$(-5.5,10.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[1, -9, 5]\\cdot[10, 19, 1]=$",
    "solution": "$-156$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $4x + y = -3$ and $-8x - 5y = 27$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 1$, $y = -7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 95 & 95 \\\\ 15 & 100 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$8075$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-11x+30$",
    "solution": "$(x-6)(x-5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-3x$",
    "solution": "$(x-3)(x)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $x^2 + 3x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.382, -2.618)) = (\\frac{-3 + \\sqrt{5}}{2*1}, (\\frac{-3 - \\sqrt{5}}{2*1})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $45x^2+121x+71=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.87, -1.82}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $20x + -13y = 410$ and $12x + -2y = 188$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 14$, $y = -10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $8x^2 + 8x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.146, -0.854)) = (\\frac{-8 + \\sqrt{32}}{2*8}, (\\frac{-8 - \\sqrt{32}}{2*8})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $62x^2+178x+58=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.37, -2.5}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -83 & -17 \\\\ 98 & 81 \\\\ -27 & -48 \\\\ 17 & -71 \\\\ 45 & -58 \\\\ 77 & -10 \\\\ -40 & -96 \\\\ -48 & -74 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -69 & 32 & 100 \\\\ 44 & -86 & -48 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4979 & -1194 & -7484 \\\\ -3198 & -3830 & 5912 \\\\ -249 & 3264 & -396 \\\\ -4297 & 6650 & 5108 \\\\ -5657 & 6428 & 7284 \\\\ -5753 & 3324 & 8180 \\\\ -1464 & 6976 & 608 \\\\ 56 & 4828 & -1248 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{15}$",
    "solution": "$2x^{15}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $8x - 8y = -8$ and $5x - 6y = 4$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -10$, $y = -9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{9} + 1x^{17} + 8x^{11}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{9} + 8x^{11} + 1x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(8,-17)$ and $(7,10) = $",
    "solution": "$(7.5,-3.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 4 & 1 & 4 \\\\ 5 & 1 & 5 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -1 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 5 & -4 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 7 & 5 \\\\ 14 & 25 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$105$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $1719$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $1$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$1770.57$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $4x^2 + 9x + 3 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.407, -1.843)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{33}}{2*4}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{33}}{2*4})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 & 9 \\\\ 1 & 4 & 8 \\\\ 1 & 5 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 5 & -4 \\\\ -2 & 1 & 1 \\\\ 1 & -1 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(5-2j) * (-12+7j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-46+59j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -9/3x + 5$ and $y = 9/3x + 2$",
    "solution": "$(1/2, 7/2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[15, -15, 17]\\cdot[-13, -8, 7]=$",
    "solution": "$44$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9746$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$22980.56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $83x^2+170x+47=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.33, -1.72}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-18+13j) * (20+13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-529+26j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $17x + -10y = -120$ and $-20x + 6y = 72$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 0$, $y = 12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{9} + 8x^{3} + 2x^{6} + 5x^{9} + 9x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$8x^{3} + 2x^{6} + 9x^{8} + 11x^{9}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 82 & 74 \\\\ 16 & 42 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$2260$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 4 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 5 & 1 \\\\ 0 & 4 & 1 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 0 & -1 \\\\ 0 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 0 & -4 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5115$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$511.5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 60 & 6 \\\\ -99 & -7 \\\\ -13 & 56 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 63 & -72 \\\\ -74 & -67 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 3336 & -4722 \\\\ -5719 & 7597 \\\\ -4963 & -2816 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $61x^2+129x+35=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.32, -1.8}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 97 & 76 \\\\ 36 & 38 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$950$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x-6)(6x-2)$",
    "solution": "$-60x^2-16x+12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-13x+42$",
    "solution": "$(x-6)(x-7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(3, -9)$ and $(18, -11)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{229}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, -4, -14] \\times [5, 9, -10] = $",
    "solution": "$[166, 60, 137]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 52 & 85 & 25 & 15 & 67 & 59 & 20 \\\\ 36 & 96 & 37 & 23 & -46 & 55 & -53 \\\\ 16 & 59 & -98 & 46 & -2 & -53 & 55 \\\\ -82 & 91 & -90 & 55 & 48 & -18 & 63 \\\\ 20 & -60 & 23 & -50 & 21 & 39 & 66 \\\\ -87 & -81 & 26 & 54 & 47 & -37 & -56 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -3 & -50 & 16 & 29 & 51 & -6 \\\\ -64 & -8 & -56 & -92 & -2 & 9 \\\\ -70 & 72 & 37 & -14 & -90 & 71 \\\\ -92 & -51 & 82 & 60 & 7 & 45 \\\\ -41 & -60 & -18 & 48 & 45 & 54 \\\\ -94 & 76 & 91 & 84 & -30 & -98 \\\\ -97 & 47 & -91 & -39 & -76 & -58 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -18959 & -841 & 570 & 1630 & 62 & -421 \\\\ -9101 & 3372 & 9111 & -2447 & -1217 & -490 \\\\ -1467 & -11997 & -12694 & -7525 & 7160 & -2557 \\\\ -10725 & -7200 & -13463 & -7855 & 2033 & -1902 \\\\ -4159 & 8492 & -2404 & 4488 & -6521 & -7793 \\\\ 5640 & -4148 & 9417 & 9137 & 1244 & 13481 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-10x-7)(7x-2)$",
    "solution": "$-70x^2-29x+14$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 1 & 3 \\\\ 4 & 1 & 4 \\\\ 13 & 4 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -4 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 4 & -3 & 0 \\\\ 3 & 1 & -1 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5593$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6424.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $4x^2+122x+38=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.31, -30.19}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[3, -8, 4]\\cdot[14, -3, 20]=$",
    "solution": "$146$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $-x + 2y = -18$ and $-7x - 2y = -30$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 6$, $y = -6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$2x^{12} + 1x^{2} + 3x^{9} + 5x^{12} + 6x^{4} + 1x^{16} + 6x^{6} + 3x^{4} + 6x^{14}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{2} + 9x^{4} + 6x^{6} + 3x^{9} + 7x^{12} + 6x^{14} + 1x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-10, 19, 7] \\times [-7, -15, -20] = $",
    "solution": "$[-275, -249, 283]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(11+14j) * (19+10j) = $",
    "solution": "$(69+376j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 4/3x - 7$ and $y = 4/6x + 7$",
    "solution": "$(21, 21)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 8x + 2 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.333, -1.0)) = (\\frac{-8 + 4}{2*6}, \\frac{-8 - 4}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 64 & 70 \\\\ 23 & 53 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$1782$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-9, 15)$ and $(10, 14)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{362}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -65 & -75 & 69 & -32 & 41 & 31 & -49 & 93 & 32 & 54 \\\\ 93 & 67 & -27 & -58 & -10 & 37 & -36 & 13 & -61 & -28 \\\\ 90 & -80 & 31 & -89 & -25 & 19 & -33 & -77 & 91 & 42 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 22 & -43 & -53 & 24 & 24 \\\\ 76 & -15 & 81 & 67 & -44 \\\\ -51 & 23 & 72 & 53 & 61 \\\\ 6 & 80 & -23 & 79 & -40 \\\\ -99 & 24 & 94 & -10 & -28 \\\\ 61 & -66 & 39 & -67 & 3 \\\\ -26 & 44 & -24 & 37 & -43 \\\\ -24 & 54 & 52 & -98 & -85 \\\\ -74 & 98 & -69 & 69 & 91 \\\\ 4 & 44 & 17 & 27 & 5 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -16119 & 10263 & 12859 & -15204 & 3558 \\\\ 16440 & -21039 & 5664 & -9242 & -4900 \\\\ -6441 & -5775 & -17357 & 4127 & 28343 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $4796$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$479.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{12} + 9x^{7} + 4x^{13} + 6x^{16} + 10x^{10}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{7} + 10x^{10} + 3x^{12} + 4x^{13} + 6x^{16}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 67 & 62 \\\\ 57 & 15 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2529$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, 13, 7]\\cdot[-16, 5, 8]=$",
    "solution": "$-87$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $12x + -1y = -95$ and $5x + -9y = -31$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -8$, $y = -1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -7x - 6$ and $y = -6x + 2$",
    "solution": "$(-8, 50)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $5197$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $5$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$5462.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[15, -13, 19]\\cdot[19, -8, 4]=$",
    "solution": "$465$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $6x^2 + 5x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.333, -0.5)) = (\\frac{-5 + 1}{2*6}, \\frac{-5 - 1}{2*6})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4175$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $10$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$6180.02$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(243)=$",
    "solution": "$5$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$-9j * (10+18j) = $",
    "solution": "$(162-90j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9963$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$5977.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-16+20j) * (19-2j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-264+412j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-8, 6)$ and $(12, 5)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{401}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(6x-3)(8x+4)$",
    "solution": "$48x^2x-12$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(3)=$",
    "solution": "$1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-7x+10$",
    "solution": "$(x-2)(x-5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(8x+4)(-8x-7)$",
    "solution": "$-64x^2-88x-28$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$0 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 2 \\\\ 10 & 8 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 0 \\\\ 0 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-11+14j) * (-4+17j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-194-243j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(13,19)$ and $(-13,10) = $",
    "solution": "$(0.0,14.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 99 & 76 \\\\ 54 & 12 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2916$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(15,12)$ and $(-5,-9) = $",
    "solution": "$(5.0,1.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(7-6j) * (4+13j) = $",
    "solution": "$(106+67j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $10x - y = 16$ and $3x - 2y = -2$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 2$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(7x-1)(-10x-10)$",
    "solution": "$-70x^2-60x+10$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(64)=$",
    "solution": "$6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{17} + 1x^{15} + 4x^{9}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{9} + 1x^{15} + 3x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $65x^2+140x+30=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.24, -1.91}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $9423$ dollars, $3$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$11936.77$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[20, -14, -9]\\cdot[17, 20, 16]=$",
    "solution": "$-84$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{3}(9)=$",
    "solution": "$2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $2195$ dollars, $7$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$614.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-4+6j) * (-12+11j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-18-116j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $10x + 8y = -38$ and $-4x + 8y = 60$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -7$, $y = 4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[15, -8, 11]\\cdot[-3, -10, 15]=$",
    "solution": "$200$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(x+8)(2x-7)$",
    "solution": "$2x^2+9x-56$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $6974$ dollars, $2$% rate of interest and for a time period of $6$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$836.88$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7x^{15} + 6x^{17} + 5x^{16} + 4x^{18} + 3x^{13}$",
    "solution": "$3x^{13} + 7x^{15} + 5x^{16} + 6x^{17} + 4x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 71 & 21 \\\\ 32 & 14 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$322$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -9/5x + 4$ and $y = -1/6x + 3$",
    "solution": "$(30/49, 142/49)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -6/2x - 3$ and $y = -3x + 3$",
    "solution": "No Solution"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-5x-36$",
    "solution": "$(x+4)(x-9)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+12x+32$",
    "solution": "$(x+8)(x+4)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[20, -16, -13] \\times [-11, 0, -18] = $",
    "solution": "$[288, 503, -176]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[3, -2, 15] \\times [-1, -3, 6] = $",
    "solution": "$[33, -33, -11]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$11 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 4 \\\\ 0 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 44 \\\\ 0 & 99 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 31 & 13 \\\\ 42 & 8 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-298$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $3169$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $4$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1267.6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-15, 8, -11] \\times [9, -16, -13] = $",
    "solution": "$[-280, -294, 168]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(7x-1)(-2x+6)$",
    "solution": "$-14x^2+44x-6$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[11, 0, 20]\\cdot[-14, 16, 17]=$",
    "solution": "$186$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$7 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 2 \\\\ 10 & 9 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 14 \\\\ 70 & 63 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(3+15j) * (-6-15j) = $",
    "solution": "$(207-135j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10 * \\begin{bmatrix} 8 & 4 \\\\ 3 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 80 & 40 \\\\ 30 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+x$",
    "solution": "$(x+1)(x)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $9x + 2y = -11$ and $x + 2y = 13$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = -3$, $y = 8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $4269$ dollars, $9$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$8506.25$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5513$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$4961.7$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-15, 3)$ and $(6, 3)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{441}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4x^{3} + 3x^{8} + 5x^{17} + 8x^{17} + 7x^{17}$",
    "solution": "$4x^{3} + 3x^{8} + 20x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -56 & -49 & 16 & -10 \\\\ -39 & -36 & 28 & 70 \\\\ -45 & -45 & -95 & 25 \\\\ -15 & 93 & -4 & -93 \\\\ 28 & 88 & 78 & 92 \\\\ -14 & 79 & -34 & -87 \\\\ -59 & -10 & -22 & -61 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -40 & 100 & -23 & 43 & -5 & -11 & 35 & 62 \\\\ -55 & -30 & -3 & 78 & -2 & 100 & -62 & -10 \\\\ 3 & -40 & 81 & 15 & 98 & 43 & -19 & -86 \\\\ 75 & 1 & 93 & -69 & 3 & -52 & -5 & -92 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4233 & -4780 & 1801 & -5300 & 1916 & -3076 & 824 & -3438 \\\\ 8874 & -3870 & 9783 & -8895 & 3221 & -5607 & -15 & -10906 \\\\ 5865 & 675 & -4200 & -8595 & -8920 & -9390 & 2895 & 3530 \\\\ -11502 & -4223 & -8907 & 12966 & -782 & 14129 & -5750 & 7040 \\\\ 1174 & -2868 & 13966 & 2890 & 7604 & 7062 & -6418 & -14316 \\\\ -10412 & -2497 & -10760 & 11053 & -3681 & 11116 & -4307 & 9270 \\\\ -1731 & -4781 & -6068 & 562 & -2024 & 1875 & -722 & 3946 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$log_{2}(16)=$",
    "solution": "$4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 43 & 31 & 6 & 88 & 59 & 67 & 4 & 99 \\\\ 70 & -55 & -76 & 15 & -12 & -87 & 56 & -44 \\\\ -9 & 29 & -29 & 32 & 66 & -7 & 7 & 49 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -6 & -23 & -31 & -20 & 90 & 28 & -85 \\\\ -99 & 79 & 14 & 72 & 78 & -32 & 0 \\\\ 11 & 7 & -59 & 14 & 36 & 89 & 67 \\\\ -8 & -70 & 51 & -28 & -65 & -15 & -74 \\\\ 63 & -27 & -87 & -39 & 18 & -26 & -92 \\\\ -59 & -38 & -46 & 85 & 48 & -55 & -73 \\\\ -89 & 67 & 28 & 55 & -92 & -45 & -73 \\\\ -63 & 2 & 38 & -77 & -95 & -69 & -15 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} -10794 & -8331 & -1106 & -5017 & -4711 & -12804 & -21861 \\\\ 6234 & -243 & 7251 & -7303 & -7065 & 2344 & -8125 \\\\ -2531 & -894 & 666 & -5591 & -6119 & -9268 & -10353 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[6, 8, 5]\\cdot[19, -4, 3]=$",
    "solution": "$97$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5 * \\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 9 \\\\ 4 & 7 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 0 & 45 \\\\ 20 & 35 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(17, 19)$ and $(-11, 6)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{953}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-15, 11, -13]\\cdot[10, -6, 5]=$",
    "solution": "$-281$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-5-1j) * (19-1j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-96-14j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the distance between $(-12, -12)$ and $(14, -20)$",
    "solution": "$\\sqrt{740}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $31x^2+82x+40=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.65, -2.0}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[5, 17, -17] \\times [-15, 18, -17] = $",
    "solution": "$[17, 340, 345]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Inverse of Matrix $\\begin{bmatrix} 2 & 2 & 1 \\\\ 3 & 3 & 1 \\\\ 7 & 6 & 3 \\end{bmatrix}$ is:",
    "solution": "\\begin{bmatrix} -3 & 0 & 1 \\\\ 2 & 1 & -1 \\\\ 3 & -2 & 0 \\end{bmatrix}"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(14,20)$ and $(-15,9) = $",
    "solution": "$(-0.5,14.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-16+18j) * (-10-15j) = $",
    "solution": "$(430+60j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(9-13j) * (13-8j) = $",
    "solution": "$(13-241j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$3x^{7} + 7x^{11} + 4x^{11} + 1x^{5} + 4x^{18} + 5x^{16} + 9x^{18}$",
    "solution": "$1x^{5} + 3x^{7} + 11x^{11} + 5x^{16} + 13x^{18}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$5x^{4} + 7x^{12} + 10x^{17} + 9x^{1} + 9x^{8}$",
    "solution": "$9x^{1} + 5x^{4} + 9x^{8} + 7x^{12} + 10x^{17}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $61x^2+183x+90=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.62, -2.38}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[12, 8, 20]\\cdot[-6, 18, -2]=$",
    "solution": "$32$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "What are the zeros of the quadratic equation $55x^2+114x+45=0$",
    "solution": "${-0.53, -1.54}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[6, -1, 20]\\cdot[17, -17, 7]=$",
    "solution": "$259$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-2,-11)$ and $(6,8) = $",
    "solution": "$(2.0,-1.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-3, 8, -5] \\times [17, 3, -5] = $",
    "solution": "$[-25, -100, -145]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(19+12j) * (-20+14j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-548+26j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 6$ and $y = 8/4x + 8$",
    "solution": "$(-1, 6)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2-6x-7$",
    "solution": "$(x+1)(x-7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 2x + 3$ and $y = 10/5x + 8$",
    "solution": "No Solution"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the roots of given Quadratic Equation $7x^2 + 9x + 1 = 0$",
    "solution": "$((-0.123, -1.163)) = (\\frac{-9 + \\sqrt{53}}{2*7}, (\\frac{-9 - \\sqrt{53}}{2*7})$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = -4/5x - 10$ and $y = 1/6x + 5$",
    "solution": "$(-450/29, 70/29)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $1156$ dollars, $4$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$369.92$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$4 * \\begin{bmatrix} 3 & 3 \\\\ 8 & 4 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 12 & 12 \\\\ 32 & 16 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $17x + 12y = 215$ and $2y = -18$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 19$, $y = -9$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} 29 & 20 & 27 & 30 & 70 & -31 & 100 & 47 & 79 & -5 \\\\ 41 & 77 & -46 & 22 & -11 & -2 & -71 & -1 & -9 & 30 \\\\ -32 & 68 & 17 & -46 & -82 & -80 & 52 & -80 & -56 & -43 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} 30 & -54 & -20 & 7 & 59 & -14 & -6 & -67 & -47 \\\\ -44 & 54 & -60 & -37 & 95 & 4 & -32 & 40 & 71 \\\\ 52 & 63 & 17 & -93 & 81 & 19 & -73 & -41 & -89 \\\\ 27 & -98 & -80 & 86 & 35 & -16 & 32 & -92 & 97 \\\\ 95 & 46 & 19 & 35 & -77 & -53 & 25 & 7 & -40 \\\\ -51 & -4 & 45 & -26 & 12 & 68 & 15 & 25 & -53 \\\\ 47 & -33 & -80 & -87 & 2 & 73 & -79 & 29 & -45 \\\\ -58 & -23 & -41 & -49 & -70 & -30 & -47 & 80 & 69 \\\\ -98 & -76 & 2 & -6 & 73 & 3 & -9 & 56 & -80 \\\\ 88 & -16 & 23 & -20 & 21 & -59 & 64 & 17 & 87 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 4227 & -8686 & -13670 & -8589 & 3658 & 311 & -11680 & 5704 & -8605 \\\\ -4656 & -1038 & -1888 & 8955 & 7502 & -7995 & 8704 & -2065 & 16770 \\\\ 768 & 12595 & -6610 & -8475 & 10406 & 9250 & -10543 & -2934 & 756 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "The midpoint of $(-13,3)$ and $(-15,18) = $",
    "solution": "$(-14.0,10.5)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Multiply $\\begin{bmatrix} -37 & -92 \\\\ 20 & 63 \\\\ 54 & 28 \\\\ 90 & -86 \\\\ -40 & 75 \\\\ -61 & 55 \\\\ -99 & -86 \\\\ 89 & -15 \\\\ -61 & 29 \\\\ -79 & -13 \\end{bmatrix}$ and $\\begin{bmatrix} -50 & -42 & 7 & -61 & -79 & 75 & -90 & -51 & -54 \\\\ -70 & -83 & -63 & -62 & 53 & -92 & 72 & -60 & -84 \\end{bmatrix}$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 8290 & 9190 & 5537 & 7961 & -1953 & 5689 & -3294 & 7407 & 9726 \\\\ -5410 & -6069 & -3829 & -5126 & 1759 & -4296 & 2736 & -4800 & -6372 \\\\ -4660 & -4592 & -1386 & -5030 & -2782 & 1474 & -2844 & -4434 & -5268 \\\\ 1520 & 3358 & 6048 & -158 & -11668 & 14662 & -14292 & 570 & 2364 \\\\ -3250 & -4545 & -5005 & -2210 & 7135 & -9900 & 9000 & -2460 & -4140 \\\\ -800 & -2003 & -3892 & 311 & 7734 & -9635 & 9450 & -189 & -1326 \\\\ 10970 & 11296 & 4725 & 11371 & 3263 & 487 & 2718 & 10209 & 12570 \\\\ -3400 & -2493 & 1568 & -4499 & -7826 & 8055 & -9090 & -3639 & -3546 \\\\ 1020 & 155 & -2254 & 1923 & 6356 & -7243 & 7578 & 1371 & 858 \\\\ 4860 & 4397 & 266 & 5625 & 5552 & -4729 & 6174 & 4809 & 5358 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$\\det \\begin{bmatrix} 50 & 60 \\\\ 72 & 35 \\end{bmatrix}= $",
    "solution": "$-2570$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[13, -5, 3]\\cdot[-5, 7, 16]=$",
    "solution": "$-52$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$x^2+4x-21$",
    "solution": "$(x-3)(x+7)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $16x + 9y = -235$ and $14x + 8y = -208$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -4$, $y = -19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5434$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $9$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$3912.48$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $5105$ dollars, $1$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$102.1$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $20x + 16y = -380$ and $12x + -13y = -228$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = -19$, $y = 0$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given $6x - 5y = 40$ and $2x + 8y = -6$, solve for $x$ and $y$.",
    "solution": "$x = 5$, $y = -2$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $7584$ dollars, $10$% rate of interest and for a time period of $2$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$1516.8$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $-3x + 20y = -407$ and $16x + 6y = 30$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = -19$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[-18, -12, -3] \\times [-10, -12, -7] = $",
    "solution": "$[48, -96, 96]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 10 \\\\ 7 & 1 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 100 \\\\ 70 & 10 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Find the point of intersection of the two lines: $y = 5/3x + 7$ and $y = 2$",
    "solution": "$(-3, 2)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Simple interest for a principle amount of $9911$ dollars, $5$% rate of interest and for a time period of $8$ years is $=$ ",
    "solution": "$3964.4$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(-7x-8)(-6x+10)$",
    "solution": "$42x^2-22x-80$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[10, -19, 9] \\times [-11, 8, 5] = $",
    "solution": "$[-167, -149, -129]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$6x^{3} + 6x^{14}$",
    "solution": "$6x^{3} + 6x^{14}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$(20+1j) * (-10-18j) = $",
    "solution": "$(-182-370j)$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$10 * \\begin{bmatrix} 1 & 8 \\\\ 4 & 5 \\end{bmatrix} =$",
    "solution": "$\\begin{bmatrix} 10 & 80 \\\\ 40 & 50 \\end{bmatrix}$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Compound interest for a principle amount of $1870$ dollars, $8$% rate of interest and for a time period of $7$ years is $=$",
    "solution": "$3204.85$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "$[1, 3, 5] \\times [-4, -12, 7] = $",
    "solution": "$[81, -27, 0]$"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Given the equations $19x + -3y = 126$ and $10x + 17y = 345$, solve for $x$ and $y$",
    "solution": "$x = 9$, $y = 15$"
  }
]